sheffieldfinancial.com 2017-03-31

# FACTS

                                                                                                     Rev. 09/2016
                     WHAT DOES BB&T DO
FACTS                WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?                 Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law
                     gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires
                     us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read
                     this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?                The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service
                     you have with us. This information can include:
                     n Social Security number and investment experience
                     n account balances and transaction history
                     n payment history and credit history
How?                 All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their
                     everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can
                     share their customers’ personal information; the reasons BB&T chooses to share; and
                     whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information               Does BB&T share?        Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes –                                 Yes                         No
such as to process your transactions, maintain your
account(s), respond to court orders and legal
investigations, or report to credit bureaus; or, as
permitted by law
For our marketing purposes –                                         Yes                         No
to offer our products and services to you
For joint marketing with other financial companies                   Yes                         No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –                     Yes                         No
information about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –                     Yes                        Yes
information about your creditworthiness
For our affiliates to market to you                                  Yes                        Yes
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                   No                   We don’t share.
To limit our         n  Call 1-888-800-3420 — our menu will prompt you through your choices.
sharing              Please note:
                     If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date
                     we sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your
                     information as described in this notice.
                     However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
Questions?           Call 1-888-800-3420
                                                                                                        C0016410002

  Page 2
  Who we are
  Who is providing this notice?             This notice is provided by certain specific companies* in the BB&T
                                            Corporate family, such as banks, consumer finance companies, securities
                                            broker-dealers, investment advisors, and mortgage companies.
  What we do
  How does BB&T protect my                  To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use,
  personal information?                     we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures
                                            include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
                                            Our employees are bound by our Code of Ethics and policies to access
                                            consumer information only for legitimate business purposes and to keep
                                            information about you confidential.
  How does BB&T collect my                  We collect your personal information, for example, when you
  personal information?                     n  open an account or provide account information
                                            n apply for a loan or seek advice about your investments
                                            n give us your employment history
                                            We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit
                                            bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
  Why can’t I limit all sharing?            Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                            n sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about
                                               your creditworthiness
                                            n affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                            n sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                            State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to
                                            limit sharing. [See below for more on your rights under state law.]
  What happens when I limit                 Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
  sharing for an account I hold
  jointly with someone else?
  Definitions
  Affiliates                                Companies related in common ownership or control. They can be finan-
                                            cial and nonfinancial companies.
                                            n Our affiliates include financial companies with BB&T in their name
                                               such as BB&T Insurance Services, Inc., and BB&T Securities, LLC,
                                               and financial companies such as Sterling Capital Management, LLC.
                                            Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
  Nonaffiliates
                                            financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                            n Nonaffiliates we share with can include government entities, credit
                                               bureaus, insurance companies, companies that perform marketing
                                               services on our behalf, and companies that assist in servicing your
                                               loan(s) or account(s) with us.
                                            A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that
  Joint marketing
                                            together market financial products or services to you.
                                            n Our joint marketing partners include financial institutions such as insur-
                                               ance companies and financial product or service marketing companies.
  Other important information
  You may have other privacy protections under some state laws. We will comply with applicable state laws
  as to information about you, including medical information.
  n Accounts with California addresses will be treated as if you opted out of joint marketing arrangements.
  n For Vermont customers. We will not disclose information about your creditworthiness to our affiliates
    and will not disclose your personal information, financial information, credit report, or health
    information to nonaffiliated third parties to market to you, other than as permitted by Vermont law,
    unless you authorize us to make those disclosures.
*BB&T Companies providing this notice are: BB&T Credit Services, Inc., BB&T Investment Services, Inc., BB&T Securities, LLC, Branch
Banking and Trust Company, Regional Acceptance Corporation, Sterling Capital Management LLC.
